





Leon Denis da Silva

Address to access this CV: http://lattes.cnpq.br/2239251029436873

Last updated 13/06/2022

Resumo informado pelo autor

graduation at Linc. Matematica from Universidade Federal Rural de Pernambuco (2007), master's at Mathematics from Universidade Federal do Ceará (2010) and doctorate at Computer Science from Universidade Federal de Pernambuco (2019). Has experience in Mathematics, focusing on Defferential Geometry, acting on the following subjects: recursive green's function, quantum computing, relações fuzzy, optimization of quantum algorithms and discrete calculus.

(Text informed by the author)

Civil name

Full name Leon Denis da Silva

Personal Information

Parental Paulo João da Silva Filho and Marinalva Vieira da Silva

information

Birth 02/08/1981 - Recife/PE - Brazil

information

Identification 7217030 sds - PE - 25/03/2003

document

CPF Number 013.384.724-10

Residential Rua Bulgária,402C Address

Pau Amarelo - Paulista 53431115, PE - Brazil Phone number: 81 8134771527

Professional
Address
Address
Address

Universidade Federal Rural de Pernambuco, Conselho de Ensino a Pesquisa e Extensão, Departame de Matematica
Rua Dom Manoel de Medeiros, s/n
Dois Irmãos - Recíte
52171900, PE - Brazil
Phone number: 81 33206482

contact e-mail : leon.silva@ufrpe.br alternative e-mail : lds.mat@gmail.com

Formal Education

2015 - 2019 Doctorate in Computer Science.
Universidade Federal de Pernambuco, UFPE, Recife, Brazil
Title: A discrete exterior calculus approach to quantum transport on surfaces, Year of degree: 2019

Advisor: Sílvio de Barros Melo

Co-orientador: Antonio Murilo Santos Macêdo

2008 - 2010 Master's in Mathematics.
Universidade Federal do Ceará, UFC, Fortaleza, Brazil
Title: Estimativa de Autovalores para Subvariedades de Curvatura Média Localmente Limitadas em N x R.,

Year of degree: 2010

Advisor: Gregório Pacelli Feitosa Bessa Scholarship from : Conselho Nacional de Desenvolvimento Científico e Tecnológico

2003 - 2007 Graduation in Linc. Matematica.
Universidade Federal Rural de Pernambuco, UFRPE, Recife, Brazil

Complementary Education

2014 Computação Científica com Python. . (Carga horária: 60h). PyCursos, PYCURSOS, Brazil

2014 C com Orientação a Objeto. . (Carga horária: 40h). Universidade Federal de Pernambuco, UFPE, Recife, Brazil

2014 - 2014 Short Term Course in C com Orientação a Objeto. (Carga horária: 40h). Centro Integrado de Tecnologia da Informação, CITi, Recife, Brazil

2010 - 2010 Short Term Course in Geometria Diferencial Global de Hipersuperfícies. Universidade Federal do Ceará, UFC, Fortaleza, Brazi

Short Term Course in Bifurcação e Quebra de Simetria Universidade Federal do Ceará, UFC, Fortaleza, Brazil 2010 - 2010

2008 - 2008 Continuing Education in Pragrama de Verão - Introdução à Analise. (Carga horária: 90h). Universidade Federal do Ceará, UFC, Fortaleza, Brazil Scholarship from : Coordenação de Aperfeiçoamento de Pessoal de Nível Superior

Professional Experience

Contract institutional

2011 - Current Position: Professor, Schemes of job: Full-time and exclusiveness

Activities

08/2019 - Current Research and Development, UNIVERSIDADE FEDREAL RURAL DE PERNAMBUCO

04/2019 - 08/2021 Management and Admnistrative Positions, UNIVERSIDADE FEDREAL RURAL DE PERNAMBUCO

Positions: Supervisor da área de Matemática

01/2018 - Current Research and Development, UNIVERSIDADE FEDREAL RURAL DE PERNAMBUCO

09/2013 - 03/2014 Graduate degree, Ciências Econômicas

Disciplines Taught: Cálculo

06/2012 - Current Graduate degree, Linc. Matematica

Disciplines Taught: Álgebra Linaer

08/2011 - Current Graduate degree, Linc. Matematica

Disciplines Taught: Funções Reais

08/2011 - Current Other technician-scientific activity, PROFMAT/UFRPE

Specification: Professor Assistente do Mestrado Profissional em Matemática - PROFMAT\UFRPE

08/2011 - 12/2011 Graduate degree, Engenharia

Disciplines Taught: Geometria Analítica e Álgebra Linear

05/2011 - Current Continuing Education, Conselho Universitário, Pró-Reitoria de Extensão

Specification: Coordenador do Curso de Férias, vinculado ao DM\UFRPE, da Rede de Novos Talentos de Pernambuco

03/2011 - 07/2011 Graduate degree, Bach.Ciência da Computação

Disciplines Taught: Álgebra Linear para Computação , Geometria Analítica

2. Universidade Federal de Pernambuco - UFPE

Contract institutional

2021 - Current

Areas of Expertise

- 1. Defferential Geometry
- 2. Symbolic Mathematics
- 3. Analysis of Algorithms and Computational Complexity

Languages

English Understanding Functional , Speaking Basic , Writing Functional , Reading Functional

Español Understanding Fluent, Speaking Basic, Writing Functional, Reading Fluent

S, T & A Production

Bibliographic Production

Articles Published in Scientific Journals

1. (2) doi: Santos Macedo, antonio Murilo; Silva, Leon Denis Da; Bezerra de Souza, Lucas Gabriel; Batista, Carlos andré; de Oliveira, Wilson Rosa Integral transform approach to mimetic discrete calculus. Journal of Physics A: Mathematical and Theoretical. (16), v.55, p.225202 - , 2022.

2. 🈭 doi> silva, L. D.; Batista, C. A.; Gonzalez, I. R. R.; Macedo, A. M. S.; Oliveira, W. R.; S. B. A Discrete Exterior Calculus Approach to Quantum Transport and Quantum Chaos on Surface. Journal of Computational and Theoretical Nanoscience. Jcs, v.16, p.3670 - 3682, 2019.

Page generated by the System Lattes in 28/06/2022 at 00:48:56.

